Stanford University, Office of Student Activities, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional material, 1978-2004; Accession ARCH.2014-052
  - Volunteer student organization files, 1978-2004
    - Inactive, 1978-2004
      - Oblique, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 68)
      - Ohoyo, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      - Off-Duty Club, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 70)
      - Okinawan Uechi Ryu Karate, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 71)
      - Omega Foundations, 1980-1992 (Box 10, Folder 72)
      - One on One, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 73)
      - Operation: Marathon, undated (Box 10, Folder 74)
      - Organization of North American Indian College Students (ONAICS), 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 75)
      - Otero House, 1992-1999 (Box 10, Folder 76)
      - Orthodox Christian Fellowship, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 77)
      - Outdoor Club, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 78)
      - Outdoor Education Program, 1990-1999 (Box 10, Folder 79)
      - Outlandish, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 80)
      - Oye! Organization for Youth and Education, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 81)
      - PAEYEPA (Preparation for Academic Excellence, Youth Empowerment, and Political Action), 2002 (Box 10, Folder 82)
      - Pagan Students Association, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 83)
      - Palo Alto-Stanford Medical Aid Committee for Central America, 1985-1990 (Box 10, Folder 84)
      - Paloma, 1993-1999 (Box 10, Folder 85)
      - Palpitations, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 86)
      - Paragliding = Freedom, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 87)
      - Particle, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 88)
      - Partners [Friends for Youth], 1983-1997 (Box 10, Folder 89)
      - Party Pros, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 90)
      - Patriots for Peace, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 91)
      - Peacemonger, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 92)
      - Pediatric Interest Group, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - Peer Health Educators [Health Associates], 1991 (Box 10, Folder 94)
      - Peer Health Education (PHE), 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 95)
      - People's Plantfarm, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 96)
      - People's Platform, 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 97)
      - People's Teahouse, 1978-1990 (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Phi Beta Kappa, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Phi Beta Lambda Business Association, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Phi Sig House, 1984-2000 (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Poetry in Motion, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Polish Society at Stanford, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Political Science Graduate Students Association, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - PoohBear Productions, 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - Pottery Club, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 106)
      - Pre-med and Pro-choice at Stanford, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 107)
      - Pre-Professional Banquet Joint Account, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 108)
      - The Pro Circle of Stanford, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 109)
      - Product Design Student Association, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 110)
      - Progressive South Asian Collective, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 111)
      - Progressive Student Network at Stanford, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 112)
      - Project Democracy II, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 113)
      - Project Heighten Education on Acquaintance Rape, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 114)
      - Project S.A.V.E. (Stanford AIDS Volunteer Educators), 1986-1996 (Box 10, Folder 115)
      - Psychology Outreach: Students for Psychological Health Education, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 116)
      - Puerto Rican Association, 1978-1991 (Box 10, Folder 117)
      - Queerland, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 118)
      - Quercus, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 119)
      - Queer and Questioning Asians and Pacific Islanders, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 120)
      - Queer Awareness Days (QUAD), 1991-2001 (Box 10, Folder 121)
      - Ravenswood Reads, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 122)
      - Ravenswood Stanford Tutoring Program, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 123)
      - Ravenswood Tennis/Tutoring Program, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 124)
      - Radical Cheerleaders, 1999, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Random Theater Workshop, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Razing Cane, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - R.E.A.C.H., 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Red Cross at Stanford, 1995, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Redwood Tutoring and Support Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Rape Education Project (REP), 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Reflections, 1993-2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - RADD, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Reformists Advocating a Culture Systemic Education, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Release, 1988-1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Renaissance Universal, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Republican Youth Majority, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Research and Practice for Children, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Residential Environmental Education Project, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Russian Student Association at Stanford, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Resistance, Action, Organizing, and Education (RAGE), 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - The Rosetta Society, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Respect, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Rinc-A-Delt, 1997-2002 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Rhythm Nation, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Romanians at Stanford, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Rinconada, 1993-2000 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Rotacare, 1995-1999 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Saathi, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - 6th Man Club, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Sahaja-Yoga, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Salangaioli Dance Ensemble, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Samba de Stanford, 1988-2000 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - SAMPE (Society for the Advancement of Materials and Processes Engineering), 1991-1996 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Sandstone, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Sanskrit and Yoga Club, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Sargam, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Sasta, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - SBSSA Consulting Club, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - SBSSA Pre Orientation Outdoor Adventure, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - SBSSA - Diversity Forum, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - SBSSA - Pre-Orientation Outdoor Adventure, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - SBSSA - The Europe Club, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - SBSSA - Hash House Harriers, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - SBSSA: Stanford Business School Student Association, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Scene Magazine, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Schools Out, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Science and Math Acheiver Tea, SMArT, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - Science, Technology & Society Students Association, 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - Scientists and Engineers for Public Out, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - Self Contain This, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      - Sequoia Magazine, 1982-1996 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      - Self-Government, Stanford Students for, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      - SERVE-Student Emergency Respinse Volunteer Educators, 1999-2001 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - Setu Sangam Foundation, 1994-2002 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - Sexual Assault Legal Advocates, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      - Sexual health Outreach Counselors, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      - Shooting Star Traveling Children's Theatre, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      - Shorinji Kempo, 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 55)
      - Sino-American Info Research Center at Stanford, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - Slavianskii Dom, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - Social Responsibilty in Computing, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - Society for Medieval Recreation, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - Soceity of Professional Jounalists, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      - The Society of Phjysics Students, 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - SoCo Club, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      - Son's Rising, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 63)
      - Sophomore Class Presidents, 1995-1999 (Box 11, Folder 64)
      - Soto, 1995-2000 (Box 11, Folder 65)
      - South Asian Preventive Health Outreach Program, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 66)
      - South Asian Students Alliance (SASA), 1994-1999 (Box 11, Folder 67)
      - South Asian Womens Health Project, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 68)
      - South Pacific Islanders United, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 69)
      - SPIRE Magazine, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 70)
      - Spectrum, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 71)
      - Speakers Bureau for Islamic Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 72)
      - Speculative Fiction, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 73)
      - Splendor on the Grass, 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 74)
      - Spirit Mind Body Medicine of Stanford, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 75)
      - Sports Business Club, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 76)
      - Springtime in Hell, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 77)
      - Standards, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 78)
      - Standing Comm. For S. Asian Studies, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 79)
      - STAR (Students Talk About Race), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 80)
      - Statistics Graduate Student's Ass., 1983 (Box 11, Folder 81)
      - Step Up!, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 82)
      - S.T.O.P. 187, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 83)
      - Stop Monopolies on Campus, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 84)
      - Street Wise Seld-Defense, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 85)
      - String Indian Sisters, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 86)
      - STS Student Assoc., 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 87)
      - Student Adventure Travel Club, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 88)
      - Student Advisory Council of the Haas Center for Public Service, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 89)
      - Student Alliance for Ethical Policy and Change (SAFEPAC), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 90)
      - Student Antiwar Network at Stanford, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 91)
      - Student Chrsitian Movement, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 92)
      - Student Committee for EE Quals Revision, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 93)
      - Student Dance Collective, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 94)
      - Student Development, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 95)
      - Student Expresso Bar, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 96)
      - Student Forum on Latin America, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 97)
      - Student Health Advisors, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 98)
      - Student National Medical Assoc. (SNMA), 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 99)
      - Student Rounds, 1995-1999 (Box 11, Folder 100)
      - Students Speaking Race and CUlture, 1991-1997 (Box 11, Folder 101)
      - Student Theatrical Resource Organization, 1980-1998 (Box 11, Folder 102)
      - Student's First, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Students Against Genocide: Project Bosnia (SAGE), 1993-1999 (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Students Against Irresponsible Gov't, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Students Against Sexism, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Students Against Tiger Salamanders, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Students Alliance, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Students Concerned for Animal Welfare, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Students Asking: what is Wrong with Our Education?, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 110)
      - Students for America, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 111)
      - Students for Bosnia and Herzegovina, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 112)
      - Students for Community Organizing, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 113)
      - Students for Environmental Action at Stanford, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 114)
      - Students for Informed Career Decisions, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 115)
      - Students for Peace in Croatia, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 116)
      - Students for Public Interest Law (SPIL), 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 117)
      - Students for Responsible Journalism, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 118)
      - Students for Sensible Drug Policy, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 119)
      - Students for the Preservation of Historic Stanford, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 120)
      - Students for Toxics Awarness and Responsibility at Stanford. STARS, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 121)
      - Students for the Exploration and Development of Space, 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 122)
      - Students for the Dev. of Democracy Awareness, 1998-2002 (Box 11, Folder 123)
      - Students in Support of Political Justice, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 124)
      - Students for Start-Up, 1994-1999 (Box 11, Folder 125)
      - Students Offering Alternative Realities (SOAR), 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 126)
      - Students for East Eurpopean Development, 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 127)
      - Summit Magazine, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 128)
      - Students United for a Democratic Education, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 129)
      - Students Teaching Environmental Agriculture at Stanford, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 130)
      - Students Untied for Research & Education About pakistan (Sure-P), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 131)
      - STUN, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 132)
      - Summer Housing, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 133)
      - Surf Club, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 134)
      - Surfrider Foundation at Stanford, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 135)
      - Surrealist Sine Society, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 136)
      - SUSEQs, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 137)
      - Symbolic Systems Student Society, undated (Box 11, Folder 138)
      - Swedish Student Association, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 139)
      - Syndicate of teh Americas, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 140)
      - Symbolic Systems Student Society, 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 141)
      - The Suites, 2000-2003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Tabloid: A review of Mass Culture and Everyday Life, 1982-1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Tanuki - Stanford Japanese Undergrad Association, 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Taiji and Wushu Club, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - TAPES, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Teahouse, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Teatro Xicano, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Techne: Journal of Technology Studies, 1988-1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Teen Outreach, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Tet Ansanm, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Theater at the Crossroads, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Text-Ex, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Thai Appreciation Society, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - The Capital Connection, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - The Coffee House Club, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - The Element, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - The Europe Club, 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - The Ivy Leaf Foundation, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - The Magazine Giving Tree, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - The Masquerade Ball, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - The Mind Club, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - SOS Mail Applications, 1987-1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - The Oval, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - The Players Club, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - The Public Policy and Social Action Institute at Stanford, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - The Revitalized English Association with Direction (READ), 1984-1989 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - The Semaphore Project, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - The Society, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - The Stanford Bio-X Club, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - The Stanford Scoop, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - The Stanford X Club, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - Stanford Wilderness Experience Active Trip (SWEAT), 2003 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - The Spring Series, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - The Thinker, 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - The Wisdom Project, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Theater about Social Change (TASC), 1992 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - ThinkPlease, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Time is Now, 1997-2000 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - Third World Forum, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Tobacco Action Resources at Stanford (TAR), 1996-2000 (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - Tomorrow's Teachers Today, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Torat Emet, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - Travel at Stanford, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - Trilogy Entrepreneurial Club, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 44)
      - Toyon Hall, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 45)
      - Trancos House, 1993-1999 (Box 12, Folder 46)
      - Tressider Union Annual Reports, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 47)
      - True Love Waits (formerly Students for Traditional Sexual Ethic), 1994-1999 (Box 12, Folder 48)
      - Tshingua Network at Stanford, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 49)
      - Tuesday Films, 1983-1991 (Box 12, Folder 50)
      - The 21st Century Dance Club, 1992-1996 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Tunisian Scientific Society at Stanford, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Two Lines: The Stanford Translation Annual, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 53)
      - Tzu Chi Buddhist Compassion Relief Organization, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 54)
      - Ubiquity, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 55)
      - Ujamaa House, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 56)
      - Ujamaa Presents, 1987-1996 (Box 12, Folder 57)
      - Undergraduate English Association, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 58)
      - Under Zine, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 59)
      - Undergraduate Lighting Project, 1972-1995 (Box 12, Folder 60)
      - Undergraduate Seminar: Native American Program, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 61)
      - Undergraduate Weenie Roast, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 62)
      - UNIHOC at Stanford, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 63)
      - Unitarians at Stanford, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 64)
      - United Campus Christian Ministry, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 65)
      - United Graduate Student Alliance, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      - United Students for Veteran's Health, 1995-2000 (Box 12, Folder 67)
      - Universal Truth Free Press, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 68)
      - University Map Markers, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 69)
      - US-China Humanities and Social Sciences, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - Vegetarian Club, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 71)
      - Venezuelan International Student Association, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 72)
      - Video Yearbook, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 73)
      - Virtual Space Interest Group, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 74)
      - Vista, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 75)
      - ViZuals, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 76)
      - Volunteers for Youth, 1978-2001 (Box 12, Folder 77)
      - Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS (VIVA), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 78)
      - Volunteers in Health, 1991-2000 (Box 12, Folder 79)
      - VTSS Students Organization, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 80)
      - Wake Up America, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 81)
      - Waves, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 82)
      - We Need a Miracle (CLASE inside folder), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 83)
      - West Lagunita, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 84)
      - What Matters to Me and Why, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 85)
      - Wildlife Conservation Club, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 86)
      - West Wind, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 87)
      - Women in Science and Engineering Lecture Series, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - A Woman's Guide to Stanford, 1988-1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Women of Color and the Law, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Women of Nia, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Women's Collective of GLAS (a Sapphic Sorority), 1980-1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Women in Management, 1994-2003 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Women Spirit, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Women's Depression and Wellness, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Women's Health Coalition of Stanford, 1993-1998 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Womens Community Center Speakers Bureau, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Women's Health Promotion Unit Student Corps, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Womens' Perfomance Collective, 1992-1999 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Womens Leadership Conference, 1989-2000 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Women's Pre-Business Society, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Women's Science and Engineering Network, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Women's Spirituality Collective, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Women's Water Polo, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - World Tribe, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Women's Peace Meditation Group, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Worldwide Christian Fellowship, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - YAY Productions, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Ye Olde Safer Sex Shoppe, 1993-1999 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Yeledim Korim, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Yiddish Club, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Yoga Club of Stanford, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Yoga Meditation, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Yoga Meditation Club of Ananda Marga, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 88)
      - You Can Make a Difference, 1986-1995 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Youth Community Service at Stanford, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Zapatistas At Stanford, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Zen Practice, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Zoroastrian Group - SAM, 1993-1997 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Inactive, Stanford, 1978-2004
      - Stanford Acapella Traveling Balladeers (SATB), 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 89)
      - Stanford Affirmative Action Coalition, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 90)
      - Stanford Action for Nuclear Disarmament, 1985-1989 (Box 12, Folder 91)
      - Stanford Advertising Awareness, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 92)
      - Stanford Advocates for Children, 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 93)
      - Stanford Affordable Housing, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 94)
      - The Stanford After Eight Society, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 95)
      - Stanford AIDS Involvement Network, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 96)
      - Stanford Alliance for Public Service, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 97)
      - Stanford American Indian Gays, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 98)
      - Stanford Animal Action Group, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 99)
      - Stanford Animal Protection and Education Society, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 100)
      - Stanford Archaeology Association, 1994-2000 (Box 12, Folder 101)
      - The Stanford Apocolyptic Theater, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 102)
      - Stanford Aristotle and Rand Society, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 103)
      - Stanford Arts Commission, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 104)
      - Stanford Asia Pacific Technology Group, 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 105)
      - Stanford Asian Women, 1991-2001 (Box 12, Folder 106)
      - Stanford Asian-American Pre-Law Students, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 107)
      - Associated Student Consulting, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 108)
      - Stanford Association for Biotech Education and Research, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 109)
      - Stanford Assn. on Latino Issues, 1981-1987 (Box 12, Folder 110)
      - Stanford Association for Medical Mentorship, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 111)
      - Stanford Association to Ratify Kyoto, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 112)
      - Stanford B Ice Hockey Team, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 113)
      - Stanford Best Buddies, 1989-1997 (Box 12, Folder 114)
      - Stanford Bhangra, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 115)
      - Stanford Bicycle Coalition, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 116)
      - Stanford Big Brother/Big Sister, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 117)
      - Stanford Bi Scouts, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 118)
      - Stanford Billiards, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 119)
      - Stanford Biologist, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 120)
      - Stanford Biotech Society, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 121)
      - Stanford Black Music Association, 1983-1999 (Box 12, Folder 122)
      - Stanford Bowling Club, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 123)
      - Stanford Boxing Club, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 124)
      - The Stanford Brewing Society, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 125)
      - Stanford Bridge Club, 1990-1995 (Box 12, Folder 126)
      - Stanford Bottom Timers, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 127)
      - Stanford Business Partners Association, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 128)
      - Stanford Business School Students Association, 1994-2001 (Box 12, Folder 129)
      - Stanford Canterbury Fellowship, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 130)
      - Stanford Center for Technology and Innovation, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 131)
      - Stanford Central American Action Network, 1983-1993 (Box 12, Folder 132)
      - Stanford Chapter Teach for America, 1993-2001 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Stanford Chang Moo Kwan Tae Kwon Do & Self Defense Club, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Stanford Chemisty Club, 1991-2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Stanford China Education Forum, 1995-1996\ (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Stanford Chinese Dance, 1989-1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Stanford Chinese Cultural Association, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Stanford Classy Association of Men (SCAM), 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Stanford Coca-Cola Scholars (Box 13, Folder 8)